AFSCME, District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series V: General Files, 1944-2000.
  - New York City Equal Employment Opportunity Policy, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation (NYC HHC): Board Briefing Book, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - NYC HHC: Special Board Meeting, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - New York State Budget: DC 37 Response, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - New York Workers' Rights Board, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Parks Policy Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - PEOPLE Committee, 1982, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Political Action, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Political Action, 1971-1973 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Political Action, 1974-1976 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Political Action, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Political Action, 1981-1982, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Political Action: City Council Campaign (Mary Pinkett), 1985 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Political Action: City Council Committee on Civil Service and Labor, 1978-1987 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Political Action: City Council Committee on Health, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Political Action: City Council Committee on Health, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Political Action: Congressional Campaign (Terry Benbow), 1984 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Political Action: Elections I, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Political Action: Elections II, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Political Action: Elections, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Political Action: Elections I, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Political Action: Elections II, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Political Action: Elections III, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Political Action: Elections IV, 1984-1985, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Political Action: Elections (Oversize), 1982 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Political Action: Opposition to MVO Contract with Vera Institute of Justice, 1989-1990 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Political Action: Presidential Campaign (Walter Mondale), 1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Political Action: Screening Committee, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Political Action: Screening Committee, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Professional Division: Leaflets, 1970-1971 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Professional Services: Reports, undated (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Quality of Work Life Program, 1993-1995 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Retirees and Cultural Affairs Department, 1971-1976, 1985-1986 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Safety and Health Unit, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - School Crossing Guards Organizing Campaign, 1974-1975, 1978-1980 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Shop Stewards Manual, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Summer Hours Dispute, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Test Manual, undated (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Test Preparation Course: Supervising Clerk-Stenographer, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Test Preparation Manual: Supervising Clerk (Income Maintenance), ca.1962 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - United Federation of Teachers: Publicity, 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - United Federation of Teachers: Strike Clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Vietnam War, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Women's Committee, 1982-1984, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Oversize Materials.
    - NOTE: This box holds oversize materials; individual folders are listed where they would normally appear in the finding-aid., 0000 (Box 60)
- Series VI: Restricted Materials, 1967-1997. (Closed for 50 years from date of creation.)
  - Local 1407 (Accountants, Statisticians, and Actuaries) (Restricted), 1967 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - CETA Questionnaire (Restricted), 1979 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Local 420 Members' Petition (Restricted), 1979 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Bridge and Tunnel Officers Benevolent Association v. Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority (Lukas et al. v. Ascher et al.) (Restricted), 1996 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 153 (Restricted), 1997 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Series VII: Audio Reels--Ken Nash Collection, 1977-1990.
  - Subseries VII:A: "It's Your City, It's Our Job" Radio Show Audio Reels, 1986-1990.
    - Bridges, May 29, [?] (Box 62, Reel 1)
    - Local 299, Undated (Box 62, Reel 2)
    - Local 299 Recreation, Jun 25, [?] (Box 62, Reel 3)
    - [Music and Songs] (Master Copy), Undated (Box 62, Reel 4)
    - [Unidentified], Nov 15, [?] (Box 62, Reel 5)
    - [Unidentified], Nov 22, [?] (Box 62, Reel 6)
    - Come to the Cabaret, Parts I and II, Dec 18, 1986 (Box 62, Reel 7)
    - Women at Work, Mar 5, 1987 (Box 62, Reel 8)
    - New York City Botanical Gardeners, Mar 26, 1987 (Box 62, Reel 9)
    - March on Washington, Apr 9, 1987 (Box 62, Reel 10)
    - Recreation Program, May 7, 1987 (Box 62, Reel 11)
    - New Yorkers at Work, Labor History, May 21, 1987 (Box 63, Reel 12)
    - Safety and Health, Jun 4, 1987 (Box 63, Reel 13)
    - Summer Recreation, Jun 25, 1987 (Box 63, Reel 14)
    - Work With the Homeless, Jul 23, 1987 (Box 63, Reel 15)
    - Emergency Medical Services, Oct 21, 1987 (Box 63, Reel 16)
    - Puerto Rican Heritage Week, Nov 8, 1987 (Box 63, Reel 17)
    - Whistleblowers, Nov 22, 1987 (Box 63, Reel 18)
    - 911 Technicians, Jan 3, 1988 (Box 63, Reel 19)
    - New York Public Health System, Jan 19, 1988 (Box 63, Reel 20)
    - Black History Month, Feb 3, 1988 (Box 63, Reel 21)
    - Black History Month (Working Dub), Feb 24, 1988 (Box 63, Reel 22)
    - Black History Month (Master Copy), Feb 24, 1988 (Box 63, Reel 23)
    - Museums, May 1, 1988 (Box 64, Reel 24)
    - Tax Assessors, May 15, 1988 (Box 64, Reel 25)
    - Museums, Jun 12, 1988 (Box 64, Reel 26)
    - Public Libraries, Jun 26, 1988 (Box 64, Reel 27)
    - New Yorkers at Work, Parts 1 and 2, Jul 10, 1988 (Box 64, Reel 28)
    - New Yorkers at Work, Parts 3 and 4, Jul 24, 1988 [?] (Box 64, Reel 29)
    - New Yorkers at Work, Parts 5 and 6, Jul 17, 1988 [?] (Box 64, Reel 30)
    - New Yorkers at Work, Parts 7 and 8, 1988 (Box 64, Reel 31)
    - Come to the Cabaret (Dec 23); Hurricane Relief Committees (Jan 6), 1988-1989 (Box 64, Reel 32)
    - [Intro and Closing], Apr 9, 1990 (Box 64, Reel 33)
    - [Intro, Closing, and Promos], Apr 9, 1990 (Box 64, Reel 34)
  - Subseries VII:B: Other DC 37 Audio Reels, 1985-1990.
    - “Negotiation” (Radio Spots featuring Baylin, Riccio, and Mariano), Jan 9, 1985 (Box 65, Reel 35)
    - “Coalition” (Radio Spots featuring Wondolowski, Johnson, Arlene Baylor, and Marco Castro), Jan 15, 1985 (Box 65, Reel 36)
    - “Haven’t We Learned Anything from the 70s?” (Speech by Stanley Hill), Oct 1, 1990 (Box 65, Reel 37)
    - “Contract Rally” (Radio Spot by Stanley Hill), Nov 2, 1990 (Box 65, Reel 38)
    - “Just Like You” (Speech by Stanley Hill), Dec 23, 1990 (Box 65, Reel 39)
  - Subseries VII:C: Non-DC 37 Audio Reels, 1977-1980.
    - Crossroads: “Women in China” (NPR Program), Aug 11, 1977 (Box 65, Reel 40)
    - The Mind’s Eye: “Cowboy” (NPR Program by Josh Darsa), Oct 4, 1980 (Box 65, Reel 41)
- Series VIII: Audio Cassettes--Ken Nash Collection, 1986-1999.
  - Subseries VIII:A: “It’s Your City, It’s Our Job” Audio Cassettes, 1986-1998.
    - DC37 Theme Song, Undated (Box 66, Cassette 42)
    - EMS Employees, Undated (Box 66, Cassette 43)
    - Holiday/Christmas Show, Undated (Box 66, Cassette 44)
    - Puerto Rico, Undated (Box 66, Cassette 45)
    - Puerto Rico, Undated (Box 66, Cassette 46)
    - Puerto Rico, Undated (Box 66, Cassette 47)
    - Wurf, Mildred and Elma Osborne, May 26, [?] (Box 66, Cassette 48)
    - Kids, School, and Drugs, Oct 2, 1986 (Box 66, Cassette 49)
    - Drugs in Schools (part 1), Oct 9, 1986 (Box 66, Cassette 50-53)
    - Drugs in Schools (part 2), Oct 9, 1986 (Box 66, Cassette 54-55)
    - Able But Disabled, Oct 16, 1986 (Box 66, Cassette 56-57)
    - Able But Disabled (part 1), Oct 16, 1986 (Box 66, Cassette 58-62)
    - Able But Disabled (part 2), Oct 16, 1986 (Box 66, Cassette 63-66)
    - Politics and Poker, Oct 30, 1986 (Box 66, Cassette 67)
    - Union Memories, Dec 4, 1986 (Box 66, Cassette 68)
    - Come to the Cabaret, Dec 11, 1986 (Box 66, Cassette 69)
    - Come to the Cabaret, Dec 18, 1986 (Box 66, Cassette 70)
    - Work With the Homeless, Jan 8, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 71)
    - The Homeless, Jan 15, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 72)
    - Talking Union (with Frank Morelli and Stanley Hill), Jan 28, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 73)
    - Talking Union (with Frank Morelli and Stanley Hill), Jan 29, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 74)
    - Black History Program, Feb 12, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 75)
    - Black History Month, Feb 26, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 76)
    - Women at Work, Mar 5, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 77-78)
    - Gardening, Apr 2, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 79)
    - March on Washington, Apr 9, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 80)
    - The Bronx Zoo, Apr 23, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 81)
    - New York City Recreation, May 7, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 82)
    - Labor History, May 21, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 83)
    - Occupational Health and Safety Administration (OSHA), Jun 4, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 84-85)
    - Summer in the City, Jun 25, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 86-87)
    - New Announcer Introduction, Promo, and Closing, Oct 5, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 88)
    - 911 Technicians, Oct 11, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 89)
    - Emergency Medical Services, Oct 25, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 90-91)
    - Music (You Can Be Happy, Celestial Choir), Oct 25, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 92)
    - Puerto Rican Heritage, Nov 11, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 93)
    - Whistleblowers, Nov 22, 1987 (Box 66, Cassette 94)
    - Domestic Violence, Dec 6 ,1987 (Box 66, Cassette 95)
    - Domestic Violence, Jan 17, 1988 (Box 66, Cassette 96)
    - Public Health System Nurses, Jan 31, 1988 (Box 66, Cassette 97)
    - Black History Month, Feb 3, 1988 (Box 66, Cassette 98)
    - Hughes, Charles and Stanley Hill, Feb 18, 1988 (Box 66, Cassette 99)
    - Eldridge, Ron and Cream Tea, Feb 19, 1988 (Box 66, Cassette 100)
    - Ibrahim, Abdullah (Local 371), Feb 19, 1988 (Box 66, Cassette 101)
    - Black History, Feb 28, 1988 (Box 66, Cassette 102)
    - Women’s History, Mar 30, 1988 (Box 66, Cassette 103)
    - Public Libraries, Apr 10, 1988 (Box 66, Cassette 104)
    - New York Museums, May 8, 1988 (Box 66, Cassette 105)
    - Tax Assessors, May 15, 1988 (Box 66, Cassette 106)
    - New York Bridges, May 29, 1988 (Box 66, Cassette 107)
    - The Other Island, Jun 12, 1988 (Box 66, Cassette 108)
    - Presidential Election (Oct 18, 1988)/Sewage Treatment Workers (Nov 1, 1988) (Box 66, Cassette 109)
    - People’s Court (Nov 29, 1988)/Holiday Headaches (1988) (Box 66, Cassette 110)
    - Holiday Show, Dec 7, 1988 (Box 66, Cassette 111)
    - Come to the Cabaret (Dec 13, 1988)/People Helping People (Jan 10, 1989), 1988-1989 (Box 66, Cassette 112)
    - Hospitals in Crisis, Jan 31, 1989 (Box 66, Cassette 113)
    - Hospitals in Crisis (Jan 31, 1989)/Black History (Feb 14, 1989), Jan-Feb, 1989 (Box 66, Cassette 114)
    - Shop Stewards (Mar 7, 1989)/Women’s Work (Mar 21, 1989), Mar 1989 (Box 66, Cassette 115)
    - City Infrastructure (Apr 4, 1989)/PSU Outreach Program (Apr 18, 1989), Apr 1989 (Box 66, Cassette 116)
    - Today’s Technology, Tomorrow’s Health (May 2, 1989)/CUNY Crisis (May 16, 1989), May 1989 (Box 66, Cassette 117)
    - Active Retirees (May 30, 1989)/Off-Track Betting (OTB) Employees (Jun 13, 1989), May-Jun 1989 (Box 66, Cassette 118)
    - Central Park Zoo (Jun 27, 1989)/Kids, Crime, Counselors (Jul 11, 1989), Jun-Jul 1989 (Box 66, Cassette 119)
    - Health Care Funding, Oct 17, 1989 (Box 66, Cassette 120-121)
    - Public Services International (PSI) Report, Dec 5, 1989 (Box 66, Cassette 122)
    - Come to the Cabaret, Dec 13, 1989 (Box 66, Cassette 123)
    - Reading Comprehension (Jan 30, 1991)/Educational Fund (N.D.) (Box 66, Cassette 124)
    - Educational Fund-Supervisory Skills for APP Test Preparation Series, Feb 27, 1991 (Box 66, Cassette 125)
    - Rally Special, Sep 3, 1991 (Box 66, Cassette 126)
    - Black History Month, Feb 10, 1992 (Box 66, Cassette 127)
    - Harlem-New City, Oct 17, 1994 (Box 66, Cassette 128)
    - Contract on America, Jan 1995 (Box 66, Cassette 129-130)
    - Post-Holiday Bills Blues, Jan 20, 1995 (Box 67, Cassette 131)
    - Unidentified Program, Jan 27, 1995 (Box 67, Cassette 132)
    - Black History Month, Mar 3, 1995 (Box 67, Cassette 133)
    - Retiree’s Association, May 1995 (Box 67, Cassette 134)
    - Community and Labor Coalitions, Jun 23, 1995 (Box 67, Cassette 135)
    - Hispanic Heritage, Oct 19, 1995 (Box 67, Cassette 136)
    - Celebrating Women’s Month, Apr 12, 1996 (Box 67, Cassette 137)
    - [Unidentified Program], May 17, 1996 (Box 67, Cassette 138)
    - Domestic Violence, Jun 7, 1996 (Box 67, Cassette 139)
    - Economics at DC 37, Oct 23, 1996 (Box 67, Cassette 140)
    - Black History: Tuskegee Airmen, Feb 5, 1997 (Box 67, Cassette 141)
    - Black History: Tuskegee Airmen [DAT Cassette], Feb 5, 1997 (Box 67, Cassette 142)
    - [Unidentified Interview DAT Cassette], Sep 8, 1997 (Box 67, Cassette 143)
    - Hidden Disabilities Interview, Sep 18, 1997 (Box 67, Cassette 144)
    - AFL-CIO Convention, Sep 31, 1997 (Box 67, Cassette 145)
    - Black History Celebration, Feb 27, 1998 (Box 67, Cassette 146-147)
  - Subseries VIII:B: Other Radio Shows Audio Cassettes, 1979-1997.
    - “Building Bridges”: Gay and Lesbian Issues, Undated (Box 67, Cassette 148)
    - “Building Bridges”: Local 1930 Rally, Undated (Box 67, Cassette 149)
    - “Public Employee”: Gus Tyler and Victor Gotbaum, Undated (Box 67, Cassette 150)
    - “Political Action” (DC 37), Jun 20, 1979 (Box 67, Cassette 151)
    - “Good Times, Bad Times”: Local 372, 1982 (Box 67, Cassette 152)
    - “Newsbeat”: Are Unions in Trouble? (with Victor Gotbaum), 1984 (Box 67, Cassette 153)
    - “Building Bridges”: Teamsters Local 810 Strikers, Jun 4, 1987 (Box 67, Cassette 154)
    - “English Language Skills” (DC 37 Educational Fund), Feb 6, 1991 (Box 67, Cassette 155)
    - “Building Bridges”: Morris Dees (Southern Poverty Law Center), Gathering Storm: America’s Militia Threat, May 13, 1996 (Box 67, Cassette 156)
    - Educational Fund and Women’s Council Program, Mar 31, 1997 (Box 67, Cassette 157)
    - HRA Commissioner/Jason Turner, Jun 30, 1998 (Box 67, Cassette 248)
    - Interview with Eric Lars Nelson of Newsday, Oct 5, 1998 (Box 67, Cassette 249)
    - Tom Defrank, Oct 8, 1998 (Box 67, Cassette 250)
    - Nita Lowey, Oct 8, 1998 (Box 67, Cassette 251)
    - Foster Care, Oct 21, 1998 (Box 67, Cassette 252)
    - Newsday/Marie Coco, Oct 30, 1998 (Box 67, Cassette 253)
    - Dennis Duggan/Lanny Sanjek, Nov 16, 1998 (Box 67, Cassette 254)
  - Subseries VIII:C: Radio Spots Audio Cassettes, 1979-1987.
    - City Council Committee on Aging Hearings, Report, Undated (Box 67, Cassette 158)
    - Meeting Union Members, Mar 1, 1979 (Box 67, Cassette 159)
    - City Workers Advise Public About City Services (6 Spots), May 17, 1984 (Box 67, Cassette 160)
    - City Workers Advise Public About City Services (11 Spots), Jun 5, 1984 (Box 67, Cassette 161)
    - Hall, Sonny and Victor Gotbaum on MTA Contract Negotiations, 1986 (Box 67, Cassette 162)
    - Employees for Improved Transit (3 Spots), 1986 (Box 67, Cassette 163)
    - DC 37 Contract Negotiations (4 Spots), 1987 (Box 67, Cassette 164-167)
  - Subseries VIII:D: Interviews and Speeches Audio Cassettes, 1979-1999.
    - Bernstein, Rachel and Gail Malmgreen Interview on Debra Bernhardt, Mar 2001 (Box 67, Cassette 167a)
    - Castillo, Luisa Amelia, Marian Porro, and Lynn Taylor Interview, Undated (Box 67, Cassette 168)
    - Claxton, Anna (Local 372) Speech, Jul 25, 1979 (Box 67, Cassette 169)
    - Clinton, Bill Speech to Trade Unionists, Undated (Box 67, Cassette 170)
    - Gotbaum, Victor Speech on Mayor John Lindsay, Undated (Box 67, Cassette 171)
    - Gotbaum, Victor Speech to DC 37 Delegates, Jan 29, 1987 (Box 67, Cassette 172)
    - Hill, Stanley and Ralph Neas Interview, Jan 19, 1987 (Box 67, Cassette 173)
    - Hill, Stanley Interview on Contract Negotiations, Oct 18, 1990 (Box 67, Cassette 174)
    - Hill, Stanley Speech: “Just Like You”, Undated (Box 67, Cassette 175)
    - Hill, Stanley Speech at Local 372 Black History Month Celebration, Feb 20, 1998 (Box 67, Cassette 176)
    - Howard, Al Interview on Corruption in City Government, Undated (Box 67, Cassette 177)
    - Hughes, Charles and Victor Gotbaum Speeches to Local 372, Mar 8, 1982 (Box 67, Cassette 178)
    - Jackson, Jesse Speech at UAW Rally, Feb 23, 1988 (Box 67, Cassette 179)
    - Kerstein, Goodie and Catherine Bruno Interview (Local 372), Jul 19, 1979 (Box 67, Cassette 180)
    - Labor Day Parades Interviews, Undated (Box 67, Cassette 181)
    - Library Guild Leaders Interviews at Rally (Local 1930), Oct 21, 1999 (Box 67, Cassette 182)
    - Mackey, [Nathaniel?] Interview on “Black Language”, Undated (Box 67, Cassette 183)
    - Mandela, Nelson Speech at Unknown AFSCME Conference, Undated (Box 67, Cassette 184)
    - Richards, Ann Speech, San Diego, Undated (Box 67, Cassette 185)
    - Roberts, Lillian Speech at Rally (introduction by James Butler), Undated (Box 67, Cassette 186)
    - Unidentified Participants Interview on UFT Contract, Undated (Box 67, Cassette 187)
    - Unidentified Participants Interview on Unidentified Subject, Undated (Box 67, Cassette 188)
    - Wildavsky, Aaron Interview (author of Speaking Truth to Power), Mar 19, 1981 (Box 67, Cassette 189)
  - Subseries VIII:E: Conferences and Conventions Audio Cassettes, 1983-1997.
    - AFL-CIO Organizing Conference, Apr 29, 1997 (Box 67, Cassette 190)
    - AFSCME Conference: “Welfare Reform for Work and Dignity” (tape 1 of 2), Dec 3, 1996 (Box 67, Cassette 191)
    - AFSCME Conference: “Welfare Reform for Work and Dignity” (tape 2 of 2), Dec 3, 1996 (Box 67, Cassette 192)
    - AFSCME 30th Annual International Convention, Las Vegas (tape 1 of 3), 1992 (Box 67, Cassette 193)
    - AFSCME 30th Annual International Convention, Las Vegas (tape 2 of 3), 1992 (Box 67, Cassette 194)
    - AFSCME 30th Annual International Convention, Las Vegas (tape 3 of 3), 1992 (Box 67, Cassette 195)
    - AFSCME Convention Speech by Bill Lucy, 1996 (Box 67, Cassette 196)
    - DC 37 Conference: “Changing Situation”, 1985 (Box 67, Cassette 197)
    - DC 37 Conference: “Changing Situation” Workshop, “New Forms and Structures”, 1985 (Box 67, Cassette 198)
    - DC 37 Conference: “Changing Situation” Workshop on Public Opinion and Public Relations (tape 1 of 2), 1985 (Box 67, Cassette 199)
    - DC 37 Conference: “Changing Situation” Workshop on Public Opinion and Public Relations (tape 2 of 2), 1985 (Box 67, Cassette 200)
    - DC 37 Educational Conference: Introduction [DAT Cassette], Jun 22, 1991 (Box 67, Cassette 201)
    - DC 37 Educational Conference: Gerald McEntee [DAT Cassette], Jun 22, 1991 (Box 67, Cassette 202)
    - DC 37 Educational Conference: Stanley Hill Closing Speech, Jul 14, 1987 (Box 67, Cassette 203)
    - DC 37 Educational Conference: Stanley Hill Speech, Jul 14, 1987 (Box 67, Cassette 204)
    - DC 37 Educational Conference: Stanley Hill Speech [DAT Cassette], 1995 (Box 67, Cassette 205)
    - DC 37 Professional Division Conference: Roundtable Discussion (tape 1 of 2), 1985 (Box 67, Cassette 206)
    - DC 37 Professional Division Conference: Roundtable Discussion (tape 2 of 2), 1985 (Box 67, Cassette 207)
    - Hospitals Conference (tape 1 of 2), May 2, 1987 (Box 67, Cassette 208)
    - Hospitals Conference (tape 2 of 2), May 2, 1987 (Box 67, Cassette 209)
    - Lesbian and Gay East Coast Conference (tape 1 of 2), Undated (Box 67, Cassette 210)
    - Lesbian and Gay East Coast Conference (tape 2 of 2), Undated (Box 67, Cassette 211)
    - Local 436 Conference: “Mainstreaming Handicapped”, 1983 (Box 67, Cassette 212)
    - Local 436 Conference: “Mainstreaming Handicapped” Speech by Annie [?], 1983 (Box 67, Cassette 213)
    - Unknown Conference: Speech by Bill Lucy, Undated (Box 67, Cassette 214)
  - Subseries VIII:F: Other Events Audio Cassettes, 1987-1997.
    - AFL-CIO Officers Election Forum (tape 1 of 2), May 22, 1996 (Box 67, Cassette 215)
    - AFL-CIO Officers Election Forum (tape 2 of 2), May 22, 1996 (Box 67, Cassette 216)
    - AFL-CIO “Union Summer” Press Conference, May 1, 1996 (Box 67, Cassette 217)
    - Clinton, Bill Health Care Plan Press Conference, Undated (Box 68, Cassette 218)
    - Collective Bargaining Meeting, Jan 5, 1987 (Box 68, Cassette 219)
    - Contract Agreement Press Conference, Oct 24, 1994 (Box 68, Cassette 220)
    - Contract Agreement Press Conference, City Hall, Undated (Box 68, Cassette 221)
    - Cornell University Labor Scholars Panel Discussion, Undated (Box 68, Cassette 222)
    - DC 37 Fashion Show, Undated (Box 68, Cassette 223)
    - DC 37 General Session (tape 1 of 3), Jul 13, 1987 (Box 68, Cassette 224)
    - DC 37 General Session (tape 2 of 3), Jul 13, 1987 (Box 68, Cassette 225)
    - DC 37 General Session (tape 3 of 3), Jul 13, 1987 (Box 68, Cassette 226)
    - DC 37 Hispanic Heritage Month Celebration (tape 1 of 2), Undated (Box 68, Cassette 227)
    - DC 37 Hispanic Heritage Month Celebration (tape 2 of 2), Undated (Box 68, Cassette 228)
    - DC 37 Nominating Meeting, Jan 27, 1987 (Box 68, Cassette 229)
    - DC 37 Unidentified Event [DAT Cassette], Undated (Box 68, Cassette 230)
    - DC 37 Women’s Committee Awards Dinner (tape 1 of 2), Mar 20, 1997 (Box 68, Cassette 231)
    - DC 37 Women’s Committee Awards Dinner, Mar 20, 1997 (Box 68, Cassette 232)
    - Financial Crisis Panel Discussion, Nov 26, 1991 (Box 68, Cassette 233)
    - Gay Pride Authors [Blank?], Jul 9, 1996 (Box 68, Cassette 234)
    - International Change, Globalization, and the European Union Forum, Feb 10, 1996 (Box 68, Cassette 235)
    - Labor and the Community Forum, Mar 31, [?] (Box 68, Cassette 236)
    - Labor and the Community Forum [DAT Cassette], Mar 31, [?] (Box 68, Cassette 237)
    - Local 420 Rally at First Baptist Church, Dec 18, 1996 (Box 68, Cassette 238)
    - Privatization Panel Discussion (tape 1 of 3), Mar 1, 1994 (Box 68, Cassette 239)
    - Privatization Panel Discussion (tape 2 of 3), Mar 1, 1994 (Box 68, Cassette 240)
    - Privatization Panel Discussion (tape 3 of 3), Mar 1, 1994 (Box 68, Cassette 241)
    - Privatization Panel Discussion (tape 1 of 2) [beginning inaudible], Jan 18, 1995 (Box 68, Cassette 242)
    - Privatization Panel Discussion (tape 2 of 2), Jan 18, 1995 (Box 68, Cassette 243)
    - Rifkin, Bernie Dedication, Dec 11, 1995 (Box 68, Cassette 244)
    - Social Security Advisory Committee Report Press Conference, Jan 6, 1997 (Box 68, Cassette 245)
    - Tuberculosis Panel Discussion, Undated (Box 68, Cassette 246)
    - Unidentified Event, Undated (Box 68, Cassette 247)
- Series IX: Audio Reels--Other, 1965.
  - 40 Audio Reels (appear to be radio spots--some are in Spanish), 1965, undated (Box 69)